这是恶魔巧克力蛋糕上加一杯龙舌兰
So it's a tequila shot on top of Devil's food cake.
我们可以取名为 撒旦的奶头
We can call it Satan's nipple.
不是不行 但是我们菜单上奶头比例有点大
Okay, but I think the menu's already a little nipple heavy.
小女子也是
As am I.
姑娘们 有两个问题
Girls, two questions--
-不要 -绝对不要
-No. -And no.
我是来看芭芭拉宝宝的洗礼仪式筹备如何
I was coming to see how baby Barbara's baptism was coming.
还有 什么酒最适合配强效迷奸药
Also, what drink goes best with a heavy muscle relaxer?
我建议奶头丁尼或奶头飘香
I'd try the nipple-tini or the pina co-nipple.
奥列格 你没事吧
Oleg, are you okay?
上一次看你这么心烦意乱
I haven't seen you this wound up since California
是加州通过法律 要求拍黄片必须戴套套
passed that law to make porn actors wear condoms.
画面美感全被破坏了
It ruins the visuals.
你们俩是承办的干妈 而我老娘
You're the godparents, and my mama is coming
大老远从乌克兰飞过来参加洗礼仪式
all the way from the Ukraine for this baptism,
绝对得尽全力[蛋蛋在墙上]达到完美
so it's got to be balls to the walls perfect.
不是说蛋蛋在墙上这派对主题不好
Not that balls on walls isn't a fun theme,
但我想办的是另一种风格的洗礼派对
but I'm thinking of going another way with the baptism party,
毕竟可是有儿童在场啊
what with there being a child involved.
如果你不介意
Now, if you don't mind,
我们俩应该是十分钟后到餐厅上班
we're not supposed to be at the diner for 10 minutes,
所以我们大概一小时后餐厅见吧
so we'll see you there in like an hour.
这杯是什么 无所谓了
What's this? Eh, doesn't matter.
无论这是什么 加进菜单里
Whatever it is, put that on the menu.
卡洛琳 你有收到我答应出席洗礼的回函吗
Caroline, did you get my RSVP to the baptism?
当然 我电邮邀请发出两秒你就回了
Sure did, two seconds after I sent the evite.
抱歉我隔了这么久才回
Sorry about the lag time.
我一开始以为又是整人信
I thought I was being punked again.
我很乐意在仪式上提供协助
But, I'm happy to help on an official level.
毕竟我也参与过我教会很多洗礼仪式
I've been involved in many baptisms at my church.
我告诉你
For your information,
我在教会有一定的地位
I've achieved a position of some stature.
蓝爸爸级别的吗
Papa Smurf?
不是蓝精灵教会
It's not a Smurf church!
我想当祭坛侍者
I want to be the altar boy.
行吧 但你不许喝圣餐的葡萄酒
Okay, but no Communion wine for you.
你一喝酒就变小骚货
You get slutty when you drink.
看啊 奥列格的妈妈来了
Oh, look, Oleg's mom's here.
大胡子比我想象中剃得整洁
More clean-shaven than I expected.
真的要这样吗 开老妈玩笑
Really, girls? Mom jokes?
奥列格
Oleg.
妈妈
Mama!
我可爱帅气又性感的宝贝儿子
My gorgeous, beautiful, sexy baby boy.
他没说过他妈妈眼瞎啊
He didn't tell us she was blind.
该不该在奥列格变成自己继父前阻止他们
Should we stop this before Oleg becomes his own step-father?
我竟生出如此杰作
To think I made this.
人生潮起之后一定有潮落啊
You win some, you lose some.
老娘状态也很赞吧
I look fantastic, eh?
我有在练普拉斯基
I've been doing Pilatskis.
类似普拉提 不过不是用橡皮带练
Like Pilates, only instead of rubber bands
是用大飞机的轮胎来练
you do it with big airplane tires.
妈妈 你又回到你当年丢铅球的体态了
Oh, mama, you're back to your shot-putting weight.
摸摸我大腿
Feel my thigh, eh?
用力捏
Squeeze it.
大力点
Harder.
使点劲儿
Harder!
好了 现在打一拳
All right, now punch it.
好像母子版的电影《搏击俱乐部》
Like mother/son fight club.
您好 我叫卡洛琳·钱宁
Hi, I'm Caroline Channing.
最近有人在拍我的人生故事电影
They're making a movie about me,
但我只是一介平凡小女子
but I'm just a regular person.
被人翻拍成电影的小女子
That they're making a movie about.
我是麦克斯·布莱克 想必奥列格跟您提过我
I'm Max Black-- I'm sure you've heard about me from Oleg
或者在抓诈骗犯节目里见过我
or Channel 7 Scam Busters.
这位是厄尔 他是收银员
Oh, and this is Earl. He runs the register,
是他让我们知道店里心脏电击器还能用
and he's the reason we know our defibrillator works.
谢谢你们把我从天堂拉回来啊 姑娘们
Yeah, thanks for bringing me back from heaven, girls.
如果你需要地方暂住
If you need a place to crash,
我的室友周末出门不在家
my roommate is out of town for the weekend.
我的确喜欢俄罗斯黑人
Mm, well, I do like Black Russians,
你也算满足一半条件了
so we're halfway there.
抱歉 厄尔 她名花有主
Sorry, Earl, she's spoken for.
她跟我奥列格叔叔好着呢
She's dating my Uncle Oleg.
如果哪天你们决定要办婚事
Well, if you two ever decide to tie the knot,
我是宇宙生活教会的证婚人
I am a Universal Life Minister.
我提了我室友这周末会不在家吗
Did I mention my roommate's out of town for the weekend?
我问单纯是因为我忘了
I'm only asking 'cause I forgot.
高列彻夫斯基太太
Mrs. Golishevsky,
李憨 你儿子的老板
Han Lee, your son's boss.
他是个很棒的...
He's a great--
不错的...
A good--
我们还没... 欢迎你来
We haven't had to-- Welcome!
我跟麦克斯是干妈 高列彻夫斯基女士
Max and I are the godparents, Mrs. Golishevsky.
我知道您在想什么
I know what you're thinking:
我看起来太年轻 完全不像当干妈的人
I look too young to have a godbaby.
我在想什么不用你说
Don't tell me what I'm thinking.
两个干妈 真要这样咩
Two godmommies? Really?
没事 我能理解 我很潮
All right, no, I get it. I'm very hip.
毕竟在座各位谁没亲过女人啊
Who among us has not kissed a woman?
阿憨
Han.
很荣幸能...
It was a pleasure to--
您看起来...
You seem--
我很高兴我们能...
I'm so happy we--
稍后再聊
Catch you later.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我本来想早点过来的
I would've gotten here sooner,
但真人秀爆火女正在上谈话节目
but Teresa Giudice was on Hoda & Kathie Lee,
而芭芭拉想看
and Barbara wanted to watch.
没事的 她有绑安全带
It's okay-- she's strapped in.
这是我美丽的老婆
This is my beautiful wife
以及我可爱女儿的妈妈 妈妈
and my beautiful baby mama, mama.
你幸会我 我知道
It's a pleasure, I know.
你从早到晚听她那口音不恶心吗
How can you listen to that accent all day long?
要死
Yikes.
要死吗
Yikes?
是指... 她"要"爱"死"你了
It means...she yikes it.
我的小孙女
Oh, there she is.
恶心巴拉小宝宝
Little baby Bair-bra.
要是我 就给她取名叫波赫斯拉娃
You know, I would have named her Bohuslava.
这名字是不是更美啊 奥列格
Isn't that a prettier name, Oleg?
没 我们就喜欢叫芭芭拉 对吧 奥列格
No, we like Barbara, don't we, Oleg?
这里没人要点个菜什么的吗
Anybody gonna put in an order around here?
不知道有多久没来过教堂啦
Wow, haven't been to a church in, uh...
我有来过教堂吗
Have I ever been to a church?
如果我遭天谴被火烧成渣 我的财产都给你
If I burst into flames, you can have all my possessions.
太好啦 我可是"超期待"成为
Great, I'm really looking forward to owning
俩大麻烟斗加一张藏宝图的主人
two bongs and a treasure map.
不是藏宝图 只是连锁虾子餐厅的餐垫
Oh, that's just a place mat from Bubba Gump's.
我也是吃了亏才知道的
Learned that the hard way.
你好啊 高列彻夫斯基太太
Hi, Mrs. Golishevsky.
你气色真不错
You look so nice.
老娘不是气色不错 是美得惊天动地
I don't look nice. I look fantastic.
这是科扎克神父
This is Father Kozac.
他将会为孩子施洗礼
He will be performing the baptism.
没错 我也是节奏布鲁斯表演团体的成员
Yes, and I also perform in an R&B group.
你可能有听说过我们 圣坛老男孩
You may have heard of us: Altar Boys to Men?
你们俩得在头上戴这个
You two have to wear this on your heads,
以对上帝表示敬意
to show respect for God.
也因为大多数乌克兰女性都秃头
And also because most Ukrainian women are bald.
举起双手 把孩子给我
Hands up! Give me the baby!
好了夫斯基 我们要开始了吗
All rightsky, should we get started?
来 麦克斯 给
Em, here you go, Max.
是类似扔出烫手山芋那样吗
What, like a hot-potato situation?
洗礼仪式开始之前 神父会问你有关
Before the baptism, the father will question you about
未来指引孩子精神生活的问题
guiding the spiritual life of the child.
比如带她上教堂
You know, taking her to church,
确保她只有在开拖拉机的时候才穿裤子
making sure she only wears pants to drive the tractor.
然后我会说一段祷文
Yeah, then I will say a prayer,
你们再把孩子传给我
you hand me the baby...
然后我为她施洗礼
And I will baptize her
比如这样
like so.
所以基本上我们就是水刑刑求这宝宝
So basically we're just waterboarding a baby.
抱歉 你知道洗礼是什么吗
Excuse me, do you know what a baptism is?
她知道的 只是有点害羞
No, she knows, she's just shy.
麦克斯 那你祷告吗
So, Max, do you pray?
她整天都在祷告啊 对吧 麦克斯
Oh, she prays all the time, right, Max?
我整天听到她卧室里传来
I'm always hearing her in her bedroom say,
"我的天啊 我的上帝啊 我的神啊"
"Oh God, oh God, oh God"
其中一次是因为有猫头鹰飞进我房间
One of those times was because an owl got in there.
所以你有跟父保持良好关系吗
So do you have a good relationship with the Father?
我还没出生之前他就跑了
Uh, well, he took off before I was born, so,
所以我对他唯一的了解 就是他懂得做明智决定
all I know about him is he makes really great decisions.
不不 不是这个父
No, no, now, that is not the father I mean.
我说的是那位
I mean that one.
圣诞老公公吗
Oh, Santa Claus?
我也想啊 可一夜之间窜遍每家每户
I want to, but every house in one night?
怎么可能真存在
Come on.
她最近脑子刚被垒球砸到过
She got hit in the head with a softball recently.
不 不是圣诞老公公
No, not Santa Claus!
你是怎么样 觉得这是一场笑话吗
What do you think, this is some kind of joke?
你们不配当我孙女的干妈
You are not fit to be my granddaughter's godmommies,
哪怕我有多讨厌她那名字
I don't care how much I hate her name.
什么烂东西
Kaputzki.
天啊 上帝啊 神啊
God, oh God, oh God.
怎么了 有猫头鹰飞进来了吗
What? Did an owl get in here?
真不敢相信我们干妈的职位都被炒了
I can't believe we got fired as godmothers.
我这辈子从未被炒过呢
I've never been fired before.
别提我跟慈善组织仁人家园的事
And don't bring up that Habitat for Humanity thing.
我们是理念不同 各奔东西
We mutually parted ways.
然后你们帮我这穷人盖房子的事也告吹了
Yeah, and then you guys never finished my house.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
看看这台新机器
Hey, look at this new machine.
就像是个监视孩子的无线电
It's like a radio that monitors the baby.
来自楼上的直播 我们是宝宝新闻台
Live from upstairs, it's W-B-A-B-Y!
这东西特别适合你不在家
It's a great thing if you're not home,
或不信任你家宝宝时使用
or you just don't trust your baby.
我猜高列彻夫斯基太太还没跟你们说
I'm assuming you haven't talked to Mrs. Golishevsky
因为你们还没冲我们大吼大叫
since you're not scream-crying at us.
老娘现在就要叫
I am now!
排练的时候发生什么事了
What happened at the rehearsal?
本来一切都很顺利 但是高列彻夫斯基太太
Um, everything's fine, but Mrs. Golishevsky
炒了我们干妈的身份
fired us as godparents.
她真的很不喜欢卡洛琳
She really did not like Caroline.
她下千年诅咒的人又不是我
I am not the one she put a thousand year curse on.
我杀价到500年呢
I got it down to 500.
她没资格大摇大摆来到这
Oh, she can't just come up here
炒了我孩子的干妈 还喝我的啤酒
and fire my godparents and drink my beer
还大聊特聊参加《美国极限体能王》
and talk over American Ninja Warrior.
苏菲 她再过一周就回去了
Sophie, she's only here for another week,
然后一切就会恢复正常
and then everything will go back to normal.
我们就不用再三个人挤一张床了
We'll have the bed to ourselves again.
奥列格 要是她觉得她有资格炒了干妈
Oleg, if she thinks she can fire my godparents
乱用我的举重壶铃
and use my kettle bells,
那我要取消洗礼
then I'm calling off the baptism.
我们得上楼把你妈摆平
We need to go upstairs and set your mother straight.
如果你觉得在接下来三小时内
And if you think that you are gonna have sex
你有得"干"
in the next three hours, oh, well,
那你还得先干另一件事
you've got another thing coming!
要等三小时吗 用手"干"的呢
Three hours? What about hand stuff?
再说吧
Oh, we'll see.
刚才她不爽时 我没好意思提
I didn't want to bring this up when she was upset,
但那是我的举重壶铃
but those are my kettle bells.
我也不爽啊
I'm upset too.
这是今年唯一一个邀请我的派对啊
That was the only party I was invited to this year.
姑娘们 帮我看看
Girls, I wanted to show you
这两件长袍 哪件适合洗礼穿
the two robes I'm considering for the baptism.
对了 你们的门铃漏电会电人
And, FYI, your doorbell is electrocuting people.
肯定是白色 另外 洗礼取消了
Definitely the white. The baptism's off.
再见啦
Bye.
麦克斯 阿憨让我意识到一件事
Max, Han just made me realize something,
除了他穿裙子会特别可爱之外
and not just that he would look really cute in a dress.
有他 有宝宝
Between him, the baby,
有厄尔当牧师
and Earl being a minister,
我们几乎有了洗礼所需的一切事物
we have almost everything we need for a baptism.
我们的确在这办过驱魔
We did do that exorcism here,
显然不管用 因为来自18世纪那个女的
which clearly didn't work because that 1800s lady
昨晚又来偷看我睡觉
was watching me sleep again last night.
总之哪儿白纸黑字写明 洗礼非得在教堂啊
Anyway, where is it written that a baptism has to be in a church,
除了圣经就没了吧
other than the Bible?
我们现在就缺圣水
I mean, all we need is holy water.
问问18世纪那个女的啊 她老是拎着个小桶
Ask the 1800s lady. She's always carrying a bucket.
为什么不能从教堂偷圣水
Why not steal holy water from a church?
反正上帝已经不爽我了
God's already mad at me.
我早上起来发现我耳朵后面长了颗痘
I woke up with a zit behind my ear.
我现在注意力都移不开那里了
Wow, that's all I can look at now.
别挤 这是我周六夜的娱乐
Leave it! That's my Saturday night.
好了 我更机灵 所以你去分散神父注意
Okay, I'm more nimble, so you distract Father Kozac
我去偷圣水
while I grab the holy water.
奶壶不错
Nice jug.
麦克斯 我等了六年终于等到你夸我[奶]了
Max, I've been waiting six years for you to say that.
现在去跟神父说你要忏悔
Now go tell Father Kozac you need to confess.
好吧 可这样我会被地狱扫地出门
Okay, but then I'll get kicked out of the crypts.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Max and Caroline,
苏菲说洗礼仪式取消了
Sophie said the baptism's canceled,
就像圣坛老男孩的下一场演出
as is Altar Boys to Men's next gig.
今天真是糟糕的一天
It's been a tough day.
其实麦克斯是来忏悔的
Actually, Max is here to confess.
而我就是传统意义上的受害者
I'm traditionally more of a victim.
好吧 开始吧
All right, let's do this.
你们的羞耻小黑屋在哪儿
Where's your little shame box thing?
我们的忏悔室正在施工中
Our confessional is under construction,
虽然感觉已经修了一辈子了
although it's taking Sergei forever.
我们可以在这里进行
We can do it right here.
突然也想不到太多需要忏悔的
Oh, hmm, suddenly I can't think of much to confess.
肯定08年时 有人像《黑衣人》那样消洗掉我记忆
Pretty sure someone Men in Black'd me in 2008.
我们可以先从下跪开始
A-ha, well, start by kneeling.
好吧
Okay.
这动作触发了我的记忆
Oh, some stuff's starting to come back to me.
总结一下 就是火光 火影 刀光剑影
Just to summarize, uh, fires, fires, knife fights,
抢劫 盗窃 持刀抢盗
robberies, robberies, knife robberies,
但真正的犯罪是从三年级才开始
but third grade is where the real sinning began.
给我点时间 我现在回忆如泉涌
Oh, just give me a second. I'm on a real roll here.
对于一个非法 亵渎上帝
For an illegitimate, blasphemous,
难登大雅之堂的洗礼会
back-alley baptism,
我觉得这布置很棒了
I think it looks pretty.
我们打算什么时候开始 姑娘们
Hey, when are we gonna get started, girls?
我2点还要主持一场理性分手会
I'm performing a conscious uncoupling at 2:00.
布置得好有爱
Ooh, this is cute.
比我之前洗礼的那地儿好多了
Much nicer than the church/slaughterhouse
说是教堂其实是屠宰场
I was baptized in.
苏菲 你看起来美美哒
Sophie, you look beautiful.
奥列格 很高兴你没系你那条阴道领带
Oleg, I'm glad you didn't wear your vagina tie.
因为"脏"
It's dirty.
姑娘们 谢谢你们偷来了圣水
Hey, thanks for stealing the holy water
为了芭芭拉宝宝不惜下地狱
and going to hell for baby Barbara, girls.
我只庆幸我穿地狱红特好看
I'm just glad I look good in red.
麦克斯 你在下面有那么多朋友
Max, you're gonna have so many friends there,
而我一个认识的人都没有
and I'm not gonna know anyone.
我们准备开始洗礼吧
Let's get ready to baptize.
我把我妈送去健身了
I sent my mother to Curves.
今天是她努力练二头与三头肌日
It's a bi's and tri's day for her.
一说到"努力"变"双"[二]
Speaking of bi's who try.
我都说了 我以为是"磨基"是一款厨具软件
I told you, I thought Grindr was a kitchenware app.
"硬"是到后来才知道 掏"球"器有两个意思
Found out the hard way that "Melon baller" has two meanings.
在开始前 我能吸两口这玩意吗
Hey, before we start, can I get a hit off of this thing?
这是香炉 厄尔 不是大麻烟
It's an incense boat, Earl, not wacky-tobacky.
我们又不挑
We ain't picky.
吸两口就给我 疯狂小修女
Puff, puff, pass, sister act.
要不是《修女也疯狂》是我第三爱的电影
I'd be insulted if that wasn't my
我会觉得被羞辱了
third favorite movie.
苏菲 芭芭拉的裙子好美
Sophie, oh, Barbara's dress is beautiful.
你好呀
Hi.
我好喜欢她的妆容
Oh, I love her makeup.
这烟熏妆谁画的
Who did the smokey eye?
好了 大家都过来吧
All right, let's huddle up.
这让我想起我曾经
Ugh, this reminds me of my time
围着垃圾桶之火唱和声
singing doo-wop over a trash fire.
好了 开始吧
Okay, let's begin.
尘归尘 土归土...
Ashes to ashes, dust to--
不好意思 念错了
oops, wrong page.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 作为芭芭拉的干妈
Max and Caroline, yeah, as Barbara's godparents,
你们愿意守护她的幸福安康
do you agree to look out for her welfare
在她胖了的时候如实告诉她吗
and to be honest if she puts on a few pounds?
当然不是现在 但几个月之后呢
I mean, you know, not now, but in a couple of months?
我喜欢能拉满一张尿布的宝宝
Hey, I like baby who can fill out a diaper.
我觉得她刚拉满了一张
I think she just filled one out.
你好呀 芭芭拉
Hi, Barbara.
都怪我
It's my fault you're having
害你不能去教堂 只能在酒吧接受洗礼
your baptism in a bar instead of a church,
但我们就是这么有个性
but that's just how we roll.
你现在是我的家人 我保证
You're family now, and I promise,
无论发生什么事 我们都会支持你
no matter what happens, we will always have your back.
对啊 你可以跟我聊男生 女生
Yeah, you can talk to me about boys, or girls,
或任何你长大后市面上有的对象类别
or whatever they have by the time you're a teenager.
你可以叫我阿憨叔叔 或者憨叔[鼠]
You can call me Uncle Han, the Han-ster.
算了 叫阿憨就挺好
You know what? Han's fine.
以上帝 圣子及圣灵的名义
In the name of the Father, the Son, and the Holy Ghost,
我正式洗礼芭芭拉·科臣斯基·高列彻夫斯基
I baptize this child Barbara Kuchenski Golishevsky.
好棒
Yay!
我们做到了 苏菲
We did it, Sophie.
我们洗礼了小波赫斯... 芭芭拉
We baptized little Bohus--Barbara.
她笑了
Aww, she's smiling.
你知道吗
Hey, oh, yeah, you know what?
她知道洗礼后 自己躲过了永恒的地狱之火
She can tell that she avoided an eternal hell fire.
你们在这里搞什么
What is going on here?
妈妈 你这么快就回来啦
Mama, you're back so soon.
该死的女子健身馆
Damn you, Curves.
我忘了那是一小时变半小时的加速健身班
I forgot it's an hour workout packed into 30 minutes.
那健身馆就是垃圾
The gym is garbage.
连双截棍都没有
They don't even have nunchucks.
什么 你们不是想趁我不在给宝宝洗礼吧
What, you're not having this baptism without me, are you?
说啊 奥列格
Go ahead, Oleg.
跟她说实话
Tell her the truth,
不然你今晚就睡中间吧
or you're sleeping in the middle tonight.
妈妈 实话就是
Mama, here's the truth,
不管你乐不乐意
whether you like it or not:
我和我的朋友喜欢盛装打扮
My friends and I like to dress up
举行假洗礼仪式玩
and put on pretend baptisms.
不是吧 我知道你有种[蛋]
Come on, I know you have balls.
今早你穿我睡袍时 它们俩还在底下荡阿荡呢
They were hanging out of my nightgown this morning.
妈妈 我们刚趁你不在给芭芭拉洗礼了
Mama, we just baptized Barbara without you.
苏菲希望麦克斯和卡洛琳当孩子的干妈
Sophie wants Max and Caroline as the godparents,
我也是
and so do I.
所以你跟这群人合伙 反抗你亲妈吗
So you're siding with these people against your mama?
是的 妈妈
Yes, mama.
这才是我那对名副其实的"硬"蛋
Oh, there's those big, beautiful balls.
真放出来了吗
Are they out?
我不知道 但我今天不能再看第二次了
I don't know, but I can't see them again today.
奥列格 你的语气跟你姐姐一样
Oleg, you sound just like your sister, Oleg.
你要在这里打我屁屁
Are you gonna spank me in here,
还是我们可以去别的地方
or can we go in another room?
因为我非常非常不喜欢 我现在穿的内裤
Because I don't love, love, love the underwear I'm wearing.
敢反抗我
To stand up to me,
你肯定很爱这些人
you must really love these people.
奥列格 我不会打你屁屁
No, Oleg, I am not going to spank you.
现在这是你妻子的工作了
That is your wife's job now.
我会把我的刑桨寄给你
I will send you my paddle.
那真是太好了 高列彻夫斯基夫人
Aw, yeah, that would be great, Mrs. Golishevsky,
因为我那个打烂了
'cause I shattered the last one.
叫我妈妈
Call me mama.
好的 妈妈
Aww, okay, mama.
算了 还是听了恶心
No, that doesn't work.
我去把圣水倒回原处
So I'm just gonna put the holy water back where I got it,
就像我从来没偷过一样
and it'll be like I never stole it at all.
我不能冒险惹神大怒
I can't risk the wrath of God.
还是我已经在接受惩罚了
Or have I already suffered it?
人生悲催 孰能分清
It's so hard to tell.
你能不能别反应过激 我们的墙就渗出过一次血
Would you stop overreacting? Our walls bled once.
神父来了
Here comes the priest.
麦克斯 你是回来做完你的忏悔吗
Max, did you come back to finish confession?
我想听听你跟男演员杰克·尼科尔森
I want to hear what happened when you were living
同住的那段故事
with Jack Nicholson.
我都说到五年级了吗
Did I get all the way up to fifth grade?
所以你只是来还圣水的吗
So you're just here to bring back the holy water?
你知道这事啊
You knew about that?
什么事都瞒不过上帝
God sees everything.
是咩
Really?
是啊 也瞒不过我们的监控
Yes, but so do our security cameras.
我还以为你没有信仰呢
And I thought you weren't really a believer.
我也不知道 我从未见过我生父
Uh, I don't know, I mean, I never met my dad,
但有时我相信或许他在某处
but sometimes I think maybe he's out there
希望我一切安好吧
hoping I'm gonna be okay.
再说了 如果没有上帝
Plus, if there's no God,
那怎么解释《全美家庭滑稽录像》呢
how do you explain America's Funniest Home Videos?
是吧 谁会在弹床旁边
Right? Why would you have a pie
放凉一块派呢
cooling next to a trampoline?
你好 神父
Hi, Father.
我们来这附近
We were just in the neighborhood
帮帮老人 做做善事
doing good deeds for old people.
他知道了
He knows.
现在的孩子们怎么说
What do the kids say?
"被抓包"吗
Busted?
对神父撒谎
So lying to a priest?
会让我有什么下场呢
What's that gonna get me,
在咱们公寓多蹲五年吗
five more years in our apartment?
拜托 没那么糟啦
Come on, it's not that bad.
我和你
You, me,
还有18世纪那个女的 就是欢乐三人行啊
and the wet 1800s lady make a great team.
她自己说的 用喉咙的那个洞
She said it herself through the hole in her throat.
奇怪了
Weird,
她明明跟我说 你的呼噜声烦死她了
'cause she told me that your snoring drives her crazy.